Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean 1957-1995
G9231.C2 coll .H4 HT
Tharp, Marie
approximately 4162 items
757 folders
19 boxes
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
This sub-collection of the Heezen-Tharp maps and papers collection contains some 4162 cartographic items and supporting materials that are related to Bruce Heezen and Marie Tharp's mapping of the Pacific Ocean floor. The item types include manuscript and published maps, soundings, reports, and other scientific data. The materials are stored offsite at Ft. Meade and must be requested advance of visiting the Geography and Map Reading Room.
Provenance
The materials were purchased by the Geography and Map Division throughout the 1990s.
Related Material
The parent collection is the Heezen-Tharp maps and papers collection.
Catalog Record: https://lccn.loc.gov/2017594025
Access and Restrictions
The Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean collection is open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Geography and Map Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Scope and Content Note
Consists of some 4162 items related to Heezen and Tharp's mapping of the Pacific Ocean floor.
Arrangement
Important note: Each Group has a corresponding Holdings Number that can be located in Voyager by Library staff members. Item(s) filed within each Group have a corresponding Barcode number that Library staff members can locate in Voyager to retrieve it from Ft. Meade.
Some Groups or titles within Groups are labeled n/a. These items either were anticipated for acquisition in early processing stages or discarded at a later stage.
The Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean is organized in four series:
Series I: Pacific Ocean: Groups 01 - 23
Series II: Pacific Ocean Special Projects: Groups 24 - 32
Series III: Pacific Ocean Geologic Map: Groups 33 - 42
Series IV: Pacific Ocean Boxed Materials: Groups 43 - 45
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Heezen, Bruce C.; Tharp, Marie, cartographer.
Subjects
Nautical charts--Pacific Ocean.; Ocean bottom--Pacific Ocean--Maps.; Oceanography--Pacific Ocean--Maps.; Submarine topography--Pacific Ocean--Maps.
Form/Genre
Manuscript maps.; Nautical charts.
Container List
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  Groups 01 - 23
  - Group 01 - Pacific Ocean Tracks, 17688140
    749 items
    - 0001 [Track Chart of the Atlantis 1955 and Shellback 1952 Cruises Off the Coasts of Peru and Chile] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Negative print. b. From 0˚ to 25˚ South and 68˚ to 85˚ West. Atlantis Cruise 221. Track of research vessel 'Horizon', Scripps Institution of Oceanography, 'Shellback' Expedition 1952.
    - 0002 [Tracks Off the West Coast of South America with Soundings Along Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Negative print. b. From 18˚ North to 20˚ South and 67˚ to 90˚ West. Monaco scale.
    - 0003 [Tracks Off the West Coast of South America with Soundings Along Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Negative print. b. From 10˚ North to 20˚ South and 70˚ to 90˚ West. Monaco scale.
    - 0004 [Tracks Off the West Coast of South America with Soundings Along Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Negative print. b. From 20˚ to 47˚ South and 70˚ to 90˚ West. Monaco scale.
    - 0005 [Bard, Horizon, MS and Vema Tracks off the West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Negative print
    - 0006 [Bard, Horizon, MS and Vema Tracks off the West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Positive print
    - 0007 [Pioneer-Surveyor Tracks from San Diego to Aleutian Islands to the Hawaiian Archipelago] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 20˚ to 60˚ North and 120˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0008a [Track Charts for Aries VII Survey] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 28˚ 20" to 29˚ 10" North and 160˚ to 161˚ East. Chart 1, for the Deep Sea Drilling Project proposed site 20-2. Aug 1-3 1971.
    - 0008b [Fathom and Gamma Data for HT V G 1a 0008] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Graph paper
    - 0009 Summary Track Sheet of the North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ to 63˚ North and 120˚ West to 155˚ East. Tracks of the Robert Conrad 11-10.
    - 0010 [Tracks for the RV Argo, Site 15] (Folder Barcode: 00275649399)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 32˚ to 34˚ North and 153˚ 30" to 154˚ 30" East. Surveyed June 3-6, 1969. Shows location of cores, camera lowerings and heat flow stations.
    - 0011 [Vema 16 Corrected Tracks with PDR Soundings] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Film negative b. From 17˚ to 18˚ North and 47˚ to 50˚ West. Nov 8,9 1969. Covers U.S. Navy Index 0504N.
    - 0012 [Vema 18 Corrected Tracks with PDR Soundings] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Film negative b. From 20˚ to 21˚ South. 24 June.
    - 0013 [Vema 2-25 Compilation Sheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 4˚ to 6˚ North and 130˚ to 132˚ East.
    - 0014 [Vema 2-25,27 Compilation Sheet] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 10˚ to 12˚ North and 141˚ to 143˚ East. U.S. Navy Index 2203N
    - 0015 [Vema Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 8˚ to 10˚ North and 162˚ 50" to 164˚ East.
    - 0016 [Vema and Robert Conrad Tracks for the Western Pacific] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ North to 20˚ South and 170˚ West to 130˚ East. Vema 19, 21, 24, 28, 32, and Robert Conrad 10-13, 17. 1:10,000,000
    - 0017 [Precision Tracks from Vema and Conrad with Depths Indicated by Colors] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Frosted acetate b. 1:10,000,000
    - 0018 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 35˚ to 40˚ North and 138˚ to 141˚ East. 1 of 11. 18 Sep 1975.
    - 0019 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 35˚ North and 140˚ to 148˚ East. 2 of 11. 21 Sep 1975.
    - 0020 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 24˚ to 30˚ North and 147˚ to 153˚ East. 3 of 11. 25 Sep 1975.
    - 0021 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 152˚ to 156˚ East. 4 of 11. 1 Oct 1975.
    - 0022 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649387)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 155˚ to 162˚ East. 5 of 11. 3 Oct 1975.
    - 0023 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 162˚ to 166˚ East. 6 of 11. 5 Oct 1975.
    - 0024 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ North and 165˚ to 168˚ East. 7 of 11. 6,7, and 8 Oct 1975.
    - 0025 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ South and 168˚ to 169˚ East. 8 of 11. 9 Oct 1975.
    - 0026 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ South and 168˚ to 169˚ East. 9 of 11. 10, 11 Oct 1975.
    - 0027 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ South and 168˚ to 177˚ East. 10 of 11. 12-14 Oct 1975.
    - 0028 [Vema 32-14 Tracks (Tokyo to Suva)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ South and 176˚ to 179˚ East. 11 of 11. 15 Oct 1975.
    - 0029 [Miscellaneous Russian Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 176˚ to 186˚ East. Areas 41 and 46. Covers 1903S and 1904S.
    - 0030 [Guam-Madang Survey by C.S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 1˚ 30" to 3˚ South and 143˚ 30" to 144˚ 30" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2201S. Track No. 259/08.
    - 0031 [Guam-Madang Survey by C.S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 7˚ 30" to 9˚ North and 143˚ to 145˚ East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2202N. Track No. 198/11.
    - 0032 [Guam-Madang Survey by C. S. ` Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 6˚ to 7˚ 30" North and 143˚ to 145˚ East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2202N. Track No. 198/16
    - 0033 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 16˚ 30" to 7˚ 30" North and 136˚ to 137˚ East. Nov 1964. Track No. 167/01
    - 0034 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649375)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 16˚ 30" to 17˚ North and 137˚ to 138˚ 30" East. Nov 1964. Track No. 167/02.
    - 0035 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 15˚ 30" to 16˚ 30" North and 137˚ 30" to 139˚ East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track No. 167/07.
    - 0036 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 15˚ to 16˚ 30" North and 139˚ to 141˚ East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N and 2303N. Track No. 167/08.
    - 0037 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 14˚ to 15˚ North and 141˚ to 143˚ East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track No. 167/14.
    - 0038 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 13˚ 30" to 14˚ 30" North and 142˚ to 143˚ 30" East. Nov 1964. Track Nos. 167/14 and 167/15.
    - 0039 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 13˚ 30" to 14˚ North and 143˚ to 144˚ 30" East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track Nos. 167/15.
    - 0040 [Guam to Madang Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 12˚ to 13˚ 40" North and 143˚ 30" to 144˚ 30" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track Nos. 167/15 and 167/20.
    - 0041 [Guam to Madang Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 10˚ 30" to 12˚ North and 143˚ 30" to 144˚ 30" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track Nos. 198/01.
    - 0042 [Guam to Madang Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 9˚ to 10˚ 30" North and 143˚ 30" to 144˚ 30" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. Track Nos. 198/06.
    - 0043 [Guam to Madang Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 13˚ 20" to 13˚ 30" North and 144˚ 20" to 144˚ 40" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N.
    - 0044 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] b. From 13˚ 20" to 13˚ 40" North and 144˚ 20" to 144˚ 50" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N. (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 13˚ 20" to 13˚ 40" North and 144˚ 20" to 144˚ 50" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N.
    - 0045 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
    - 0046 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649363)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 13˚ 30" to 13˚ 33" North and 144˚ 45" to 144˚ 49" East. Dec 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2203N.
    - 0047 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
    - 0048 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 17˚ to 18˚ North and 134˚ 30" to 136˚ East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2304N. Track Nos. 136/20, 137/16, 166/05, and 167/01.
    - 0049 [Hong Kong to Guam Survey by C. S. Mercury] (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 19˚ 30" to 20˚ North and 123˚ to 125˚ East. Nov 1964. U.S. Navy Index 2404N. Track No. 135/15.
    - 0050 [Multiple Pacific Ocean Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Tracks by the U.S.S. Glacier, Arnco and Adisto.
    - 0051 Scripps Track Index of South Central East Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 15˚ North to 20˚ South and 80˚ to 125˚ West. 1 of 2.
    - 0052 Scripps Track Chart of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
      a. Paper. b. From 0˚ to 42˚ North and 100˚ to 130˚ East. Sheet 5 of 21.
    - 0053 Scripps Track Chart of Bathymetric Data - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649351)
    - 0054 Scripps Track Chart of Magnetic Data - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
      a. Paper. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Sheet 6 of 21.
    - 0055 Scripps Track Chart of Bathymetric Data - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
    - 0056 Scripps Track of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
    - 0057 Scripps Track of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 140˚ to 170˚ West. Sheet 8 of 21.
    - 0058 Scripps Track of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 110˚ to 140˚ West. Sheet 9 of 21. Special track chart No. 1, 2 and 4.
    - 0059 Scripps Track Chart of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - North Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 0027564934A)
      a. Film negative b. From 0˚ to 40˚ North and 80˚ to 110˚ West. Sheet 10 of 21. Special track chart No. 4.
    - 0060 Scripps Track Chart of Bathymetric Data - South Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
      a. Paper. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ South and 130˚ to 160˚ West. Sheet 11 of 21.
    - 0061 Scripps Track Chart of Magnetic Data - South Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
      a. Paper. b. From 0˚ to 40˚ South and 130˚ to 160˚ East. Sheet 11 of 21.
    - 0062 Scripps Track Chart of Seismic Reflection Profiles and Refraction Stations - South Pacific Ocean (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
    - 0063 [Scripps Tracks of Southwest Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
      a. Paper. b. From 20˚ to 50˚ South and 150˚ to 170˚ East
    - 0064 [D. V. Glomar Challenger Leg VI] (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
      a. Frosted acetate b. Drill sites 44, 45 - 59 and 60. Reprinted in the Initial Reports of the Deep Sea Drilling Project, Vol. 6, 1970 by courtesy of the Geological Society of America.
    - 0065 [Plot of 0064 on Physiographic Diagram of the Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649338)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 110˚ East to 150˚ West. Track from the Thomas Washington from Hawaii to Japan.
    - 0066 Distribution of Selected Echo- Sounding Traverses (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Film negative b. From 48˚ to 57˚ South and 159˚ to 179˚ East. Vicinity of Campbell Island.
    - 0067 [Miscellaneous Track Vicinity of Japan] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Film negative b. From 25˚ to 45˚ North and 135˚ to 165˚ East.
    - 0068 [Tracks South of Australia] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Film negative b. Monaco scale. Made 24 Jan 1975
    - 0069 [Tracks and Contours - Eastern South Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Film negative b. From 35˚ North to 67˚ South and 70˚ to 110˚ West.
    - 0070 [Tracks and Stations - Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ to 35˚ North and 140˚ to 160˚ East.
    - 0071 [Tracks off the Western and Southern Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 35˚ to 63˚ South and 40˚ to 80˚ West.
    - 0072 [Computerized Plot of Pacific Ocean Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Tracing aper b. From 30˚ to 60˚ South and 90˚ to 130˚ West.
    - 0073 [Central Pacific Ocean Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 60˚ North to 45˚ South and 148˚ to 165˚ West.
    - 0074 [Multiple Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 12˚ to 23˚ North and 109˚ to 121˚ East.
    - 0075 [Computerized Plot of Pacific Ocean Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649326)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0076 [UM Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Film negative b. From 25˚ North to 35˚ South and 100˚ to 160˚ East.
    - 0077 [UM Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Paper. b. From 25˚ North to 35˚ South and 100˚ to 160˚ East.
    - 0078 [Unidentified Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Paper. b. From 40˚ North to 40˚ South and 120˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0079 [Vema Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 30˚ North to 10˚ South and 120˚ to 155˚ East.
    - 0080 [Vema Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 30˚ North to 10˚ South and 135˚ to 165˚ East.
    - 0081 [Vema Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 15˚ North to 10˚ South and 165˚ to 180˚ East. Map 6, North.
    - 0082 [Vema Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 11˚ to 50˚ South and 165˚ East to 170˚ West.
    - 0083 [Unidentified Tracks Vicinity New Zealand] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 20˚ to 60˚ South and 160˚ East to 120˚ West.
    - 0084 [Unidentified Tracks Off West Coast of South America] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 20˚ to 60˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0085 [Unidentified Tracks South of New Zealand] (Folder Barcode: 00275649314)
      a. Positive print b. From 60˚ to 79˚ South and 160˚ East to 160˚ West.
    - 0086 [Conrad Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649302)
      a. Film negative b. From 30˚ North to 10˚ South and 105˚ to 165˚ East.
    - 0087 [Conrad and Vema Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649302)
      a. Film negative b. From 63˚ North to 10˚ South and 100˚ to 165˚ East.
    - 0088 [Conrad, Eltanin and Vema Tracks - South Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649302)
      a. Film negative b. From 11˚ to 60˚ South and 100˚ West to 165˚ East.
    - 0089 [South Central Pacific Ocean Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649302)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 45˚ to 72˚ South and 110˚ East to 170˚ West. Plotted over U.S. Navy Index grid.
    - 0090 [Scripps 'Midpac' Track - P85] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ North and 150˚ West to 120˚ East. Pacific ocean northwest sheet.
    - 0091 [Miscellaneous Pioneer Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. Pacific Northwest sheet
    - 0092 [Scripps 'Midpac', AT&T and 'Surveyor' Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 0˚ North to 30˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East. Tracks from Snellius, AUS MS, Downwind, Vema 18, USMS and Capricorn. On control map 2/10/65 - DCJ. Howard Foster.
    - 0093 [Monsoon and Vema Tracks - West Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East.
    - 0094 [Unidentified Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Pacific northeast sheet.
    - 0095 [Vema 2-29 Track] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ North and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Pacific northeast sheet.
    - 0096 [Scripps 'Midpac' 285 and AT&T Surveyor Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
    - 0097 [Eltanin, Vema, Eastwind, Glacier, Dolphin and SIO Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East. Pacific southwest sheet.
    - 0098 [Glacier and Argo-Monsoon Expedition Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649296)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East. Expedition - Jan 1961.
    - 0099 [Pacific Ocean Tracks and Camera Stations] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Acetate b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West. Pacific southwest sheet.
    - 0100 [Pacific Ocean Tracks and Camera Stations] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West. Pacific southwest sheet.
    - 0101 [Unidentified Cruise Tracks - East Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Frosted acetate b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0102 [Eastwind, Eltanin and Vema Tracks - Southeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0103 [Arneb and Adisto Tracks - Southeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Arned - 2/11/61, Adisto - 11/20/60
    - 0104 [Eltanin and Conrad Tracks - Southeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West. Eltanin 19-22, Conrad 8 and 9.
    - 0105 [Track Chart Off Western Australia] (Folder Barcode: 00275649284)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 8˚ to 28˚ South and 110˚ to 130˚ East. Note: "Hi Gang. Get this here map reduced to GEBCO scale and add to the northwest Australian margin. Thank you, troops. Hang in there! Alan Lowrie."
    - 0106 [Track of Vema 34 (Fiji to Guam) and Thomas Washington (Hawaii to Japan)] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Paper. b. From 30˚ North to 40˚ South and 150˚ West to 110˚ East. Plotted on Physiographic Diagram of the Western Pacific Ocean.
    - 0107 [Scripps and Vema Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Tracing paper b. From 0˚ to 47˚ South and 170˚ East to 60˚ West.
    - 0108 [Miscellaneous Tracks] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 40˚ to 72˚ South and 20˚ to 110˚ East.
    - 0109 [Unidentified Tracks - Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 20˚ to 55˚ North and 105˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0110 [Unidentified Tracks - Northeast Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 17˚ to 60˚ North and 100˚ to 175˚ West.
    - 0111 [Unidentified Tracks -Western Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649272)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 20˚ North to 50˚ South and 125˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0112 [Unidentified Tracks - Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 50˚ North to 50˚ South and 125˚ to 180˚ West.
    - 0113 [Unidentified Tracks - East Central Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ North to 50˚ South and 70˚ to 125˚ West.
    - 0114 [Australian Tracks - Southwestern Pacific Ocean] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 5˚ to 35˚ South and 170˚ West to 150˚ East.
    - 0115 [Gulf of Panama Tracks and Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ North to 8˚ South and 67˚ to 97˚ West. Sheet I
    - 0116 [Gulf of Panama Tracks and Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 18˚ North to 8˚ South and 67˚ to 97˚ West. Sheet II
    - 0117 [West Coast of South America Tracks and Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 12˚ to 39˚ South and 67˚ to 90˚ West. Sheet III.
    - 0118 [West Coast of South America Tracks and Profiles] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Ozalid. b. From 12˚ to 39˚ South and 67˚ to 90˚ West. Sheet IV.
    - 0119 [Miscellaneous Tracks with Time Shown Near the Faraulep Atoll] (Folder Barcode: 00275649260)
      a. Paper. b. From 6˚ 30" to 13˚ 30" North and 134˚ to 145˚ East.